Alex@What kind of photo frame is this?
Alex@Where did this ugly guy come from? He's so ugly.
Megan@What a weird thing.
Emily@Where should we put this thing?
Victoria@Emily
Victoria@Let's put it here.
Emily@What is this thing?
Emily@Oh no
Emily@Did the previous tenant not clean out their stuff?
Megan@Hey, Emily
Megan@Did you hurt your hand just now?
Emily@It's fine
Emily@Grace
Emily@What should I do with the broken glass?
Emily@It just fell
Grace@Oh! Don't worry
Grace@I'll go get some newspaper now
Grace@Leave it to me
Emily@Okay
Samantha@Are you sure you're not hurt?
Megan@I want to order some drinks
Megan@I'm so thirsty
Megan@Does anyone else want to order drinks?
Victoria@I'm so thirsty
Samantha@I want bubble milk tea without the bubbles
Samantha@No sugar
Alex@Wait a second
Alex@What's that?
Alex@This place?
Victoria@Great!
Victoria@This one's not bad
@This place? - This place is pretty good
Samantha@This one
Megan@Honey green tea
Alex@Honey green tea
Megan@You know my usual
Alex@Black tea latte, less sugar, no ice
Samantha@Alright, then...
Samantha@Orange green tea
Samantha@Slightly sweet, less ice
Alex@What do you want?
Victoria@I also want a black tea latte
Victoria@No sugar, no ice
Alex@Okay
Alex@Alright
Alex@Hey, what did you say you wanted?
Emily@Honey green tea
Alex@Oh, sorry
@No sugar - She doesn't know what she wants
Samantha@Sugar-free what kind of ice?
Megan@Let's order her some black tea.
Alex@Yeah, let's get her black tea.
@Right. - Probably with less ice too.
Alex@Less sugar, less ice.
Samantha@I'm back.
Samantha@What do you want to drink?
Megan@I'm ordering drinks.
Samantha@So, what do you want to drink?